<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="terms_content">"Terms of Use
Terms and Conditions
These terms of and conditions of use ("Terms of Use") set out the terms on which you may access and use our Website, download and use the "Jobpedia" mobile application ("App") and access our services, whether through the Website, the App, or made available by us or one of our group companies by other means from time to time ("Services").
The Website and the App are owned and operated by OneJob Group Limited ("Jobpedia" / "Company" / "we" / "us" / "our") (a limited liability company incorporated under the laws of Hong Kong) or by one of our group companies, and are made available to you subject to these Terms of Use. Services may be offered or provided by us or by one of our group companies. The use of certain Services offered through the Website or App may be subject to specific terms and conditions which may substitute, complete and / or modify these Terms of Use. Therefore, prior to the use of such services, you must also carefully read and accept the corresponding terms and conditions for those Services.
By using the Website and/or the App and/or any Services, you are deemed to accept these Terms of Use and any additional terms and conditions which advise you apply to the Services you choose to receive. If you do not agree to this, you may not use the Website, the App or receive the relevant Services. The use of the Website or App means acceptance of the terms and conditions that apply when you access it. We therefore recommend that you periodically review these Terms of Use for any changes or updates. The Company reserves the right to modify the terms and conditions of this Agreement or its policies relating to the Service or Application at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement on the Service or Application. Continued use of the service or application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes

Electronic communications:
Acceptance of these Terms of Use or specific terms and conditions for the use of any of our Services, implies your express authorization for us to send you the electronic communications indicated in the following paragraph to your home, mobile phone and email address. Such authorization includes sending commercial and advertising communications related to products and services from us and other portals related to this platform as well as third parties and their portals (including our group companies). We currently send the following communications via email or SMS or mobile notification:
suggestions and job alerts;
a newsletter with tips for finding employment, reports, trends, etc.;
commercial communications (for advertising, market research and with commercial prospects).
By completing and sending the electronic registration form you consent to us sending electronic communications related to the field of training and employment.
The Service is a platform for enabling connections between Users for the fulfillment of jobs, but the Company is not responsible for the performance of Users, nor does it have control over the quality, timing, legality, failure to provide, or any other aspect whatsoever of Job Clients, nor of the integrity, responsibility or any of the actions or omissions whatsoever of any Users. Company does not have control over the quality, timing or legality of jobs delivered by its users.
Vetting
Clients and Users may be subject to an extensive vetting process before they register and during their use of the Service, including but not limited to identity verification and comprehensive criminal and background checks, using third party services as appropriate. Users hereby give consent to Company to conduct background checks as often as required in compliance with laws within the governing jurisdiction.
Although Company may perform background checks of Users, as outlined above, Company cannot confirm that each User is who they claim to be and therefore, Company cannot and does not assume any responsibility for the accuracy or reliability identity or background check information or any information provided through the Service.
When interacting with other Users, you should exercise caution and common sense to protect your personal safety and property. Neither Company nor its affiliates or licensors is responsible for the conduct, whether online or offline, of any user of the service and you hereby release the Company and its affiliates or licensors from any liability related thereto. Company and its affiliates and licensors will not be liable for any claim, injury or damage arising in connection with your use of the service

Our Rights Following Registration
By providing us with your personal information on registration, you agree that we and our group companies can contact you during normal business hours by phone or email or other appropriate means regarding your account.
By submitting any content to the App, you grant us and our group companies a royalty free, perpetual, irrevocable, sub-licensable, non-exclusive, right and licence to use, reproduce, modify, publish, translate, transmit, communicate, display or create any derivative works from such content. Where such content includes your Resume this will only be in relation to your use of the Services and in accordance with any additional terms and conditions which expressly apply to such Services. We reserve the right to make inactive or delete at any time and without prior notice any content on the App. In the event that we make inactive or delete any of your content on the App we shall use reasonable endeavours, but are not obliged, to contact you in advance.
We reserve the right to remove any content (including without limitation any Resume or information relating to a job vacancy) which we deem to be inaccurate, misleading, deceptive, likely to mislead or deceive or of an unacceptable standard.
We may suspend or cancel your registration immediately if you breach any of your obligations under these Terms of Use or under any other terms and conditions which apply to any services provided to you, or otherwise at our reasonable discretion.
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to pursue all of our legal remedies, including but not limited to deletion of your content (including without limitation any Resume) from the App and immediate termination of your registration with or without ability to access the App and/or any service provided to you by us, upon any breach by you of the Terms of Use, these Worker Engagement Terms or any other terms and conditions applicable to your use of any services provided by us or any of our group companies, if we are unable to verify or authenticate any consent you submit to the App.

Acceptable use of the service
The Service may contain profiles, email systems, blogs, message boards, applications, job postings, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities and/or other message or communication facilities that allow Users to communicate with other Users. You may only use such community areas to send and receive messages and material that are relevant and proper to the applicable forum.
All Users of the Site, whether or not registered as a Member, shall be prohibited from using the Site in any manner which:
Contains or involves information which is incomplete, false, inaccurate, misleading, fraudulent, defamatory, libelous, obscene, discriminatory, harassing, threatening, abusive, hateful, racist, illegal, improper, offensive, or otherwise unrelated to recruitment/job seeking purposes (including without limitation by soliciting donations or businesses, launching irrelevant advertisements, sending unsolicited e-mails or conducting direct or indirect marketing);
Infringes the Intellectual Property Rights or proprietary rights of Company, other Users or any third parties, or violates the privacy, publicity or other personal rights of others;
Does not have the permission from the owner of the information, the account or the system;
Causes viruses, corrupted files or other materials to interrupt, damage or limit the operation, or violate the security of the Site, or tamper or interfere with the Services to any User;
Violates the Terms and Conditions, the Privacy Policy or any applicable laws and regulations of Hong Kong or other relevant jurisdictions, and without prejudice, Company may, without notice, disable the publication of, or remove or amend any information provided by such User, if the information is considered to be in violation of any of the restrictions stipulated under this

Termination and Suspension
The Contract between Company and you is concluded for an indefinite period.
Company may terminate or suspend your right to use the Service at any time for any reason by providing you with written or email notice of such termination, and termination will be effective immediately upon delivery of such notice.
Without limitation, Company may terminate or suspend your right to use the Service if you breach any term of this Agreement (including the Marketplace Guidelines) or any policy of Company posted through the Service from time to time, or if Company otherwise finds that you have engaged in inappropriate and/or offensive behavior. If Company terminates or suspends your right to use the Service for any of these reasons, you will not be entitled to any refund of unused balance in your account. If Company terminates or suspends your account for any reason, you are prohibited from registering and creating a new account under your name, a fake or borrowed name, or the name of any third party, even if you may be acting on behalf of the third party. In addition to terminating or suspending your account, Company reserves the right to take appropriate legal action, including without limitation pursuing civil, criminal, and injunctive redress.
Even after your right to use the Service is terminated or suspended, this Agreement will remain enforceable against you.
You may terminate this Agreement at any time by ceasing all use of the Service. All sections which by their nature should survive the expiration or termination of this Agreement shall continue in full force and effect subsequent to and notwithstanding the expiration or termination of this Agreement.

Security
You must register with Company and create an account to use the Service. You are the sole authorized user of your account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password and account number provided by you or Company for accessing the Service. You are solely and fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. Company has no control over the use of any User’s account and expressly disclaims any liability derived therefrom. Should you suspect that any unauthorized party may be using your password or account or you suspect any other breach of security, you will contact Company immediately.
By providing your mobile phone number and using the Service, you hereby affirmatively consent to our use of your mobile phone number for calls and texts in order to perform and improve upon the Service. Company will not assess any charges for calls or texts, but standard message charges or other charges from your wireless carrier may apply.
We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any activity and content associated with the Website and App. We may investigate any reported violation of these Terms of Use or complaints and take any action that we deem appropriate (which may include, but is not limited to, issuing warnings, suspending, terminating or attaching conditions to your access and/or removing any materials from the Website or App).



Personal Information
Your Information” is defined as any information and materials you provide to Company or other Users in connection with your registration for and use of the Service, including without limitation that posted or transmitted for use in Public Areas. You are solely responsible for Your Information, and we act merely as a passive conduit for your online distribution and publication of Your Information. The information and materials described in this Section, as provided by each User, is collectively referred to herein as “User Generated Content.” You hereby represent and warrant to Company that Your Information (a) will not be false, inaccurate, incomplete or misleading; (b) will not be fraudulent or involve the sale of counterfeit or stolen items; (c) will not infringe any third party’s copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary right or rights of publicity or privacy; (d) will not violate any law, statute, ordinance, or regulation (including without limitation those governing export control, consumer protection, unfair competition, anti-discrimination or false advertising); (e) will not be defamatory, libelous, unlawfully threatening, or unlawfully harassing; (f) will not be obscene or contain child pornography or be harmful to minors; (g) will not contain any viruses, Trojan Horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots or other computer programming routines, and/ or malwares, among other things, that are intended to damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information; and (h) will not create liability for Company or cause Company to lose (in whole or in part) the services of its ISPs or other Clients or suppliers.
The Service hosts User Generated Content relating to reviews of specific Users. Such reviews are opinions and not the opinion of Company, have not been verified or approved by Company and each Client should undertake their own research to be satisfied that a specific User is the right person for a Job. You agree that Company is not liable for any User Generated Content.
You hereby grant Company a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sublicensable (through multiple tiers) right to exercise all copyright, publicity rights, and any other rights you have in Your Information, in any media now known or not currently known in order to perform and improve upon the Service.
Each User who provides to the Company any videotape, film, record, photograph, voice, or all related instrumental, musical, or other sound effects, in exchange for the right to use the Service, hereby irrevocably grants to the Company the non-exclusive, fully-paid, royalty-free, transferable, sublicensable, worldwide, unrestricted, and perpetual right to:
Use any videotape, film, record or photograph that such User provides to the Company, and use, reproduce, modify, or creative derivatives of such User picture, silhouette and other reproductions of their physical likeness (as the same may appear in any still camera photograph and/or motion picture film or video) (collectively the “Physical Likeness”), in and in connection with the exhibition, distribution, display, performance, transmission, broadcasting on any and all media, including, without limitation, the internet, of any videos or images of such User in connection with the Service.
Reproduce in all media any recordings of such User’s voice, and all related instrumental, musical, or other sound effects (collectively, the “Voice”), made in connection with the Service.
Use, and permit to be used, such User’s Physical Likeness and Voice in the advertising, marketing, and/or publicizing of the Service in any media.
Use, and permit to be used, such User’s name and identity in connection with the Service.
Each User hereby waives all rights and releases the Company from, and shall neither sue nor bring any proceeding against any such parties for, any claim or cause of action, whether now known or unknown, for defamation, invasion of right to privacy, publicity or personality or any similar matter, or based upon or relating to the use and exploitation of such User’s identity, likeness or voice in connection with the Service.
Each User acknowledges that the Company shall not owe any financial or other remuneration for using the recordings provided hereunder by such User, either for initial or subsequent transmission or playback, and further acknowledges that the Company is not responsible for any expense or liability incurred as a result of such User’s recordings or participation in any recordings, including any loss of such recording data
Personal Information Collection Statement
Personal data collection for job application are voluntary. However, user verification will only be conducted upon complete data submission. Data collected include but not limited to photos, official identification documents, address proof, bank account number (for payroll transfer). Data are used to ensure users’ legitimacy and the right to work in their local jurisdiction as well as for payroll services.
The personal data collected from you will be used for purposes relating to job application. The company may use it to: 1) to establish and maintain employment relationship; 2) to assess and administer your job application and be involved in the provision and administration of insurance, superannuation/ retirement funds, employee benefits; 3) to inform you of new job opportunities and provide training and related information; 4. marketing promotion; 5. to maintain contractual and statutory obligations; 6. to prepare statistical data; 7. to provide compensation and benefit, salary, appraisal, promotion and career development; 8. to address and respond to legal claims and actions, compliance with court orders and other legal obligations and regulatory requirements. You consent to the Company making any necessary enquires for purposes relating to job application and for the verification of the information given above. You understand that the Company may disclose and transfer Personal Data to our subsidiaries, associated companies and/ or the clients who we consider appropriate in connection with recruitment and selection purposes.

Copyright
You acknowledge that Confidential Information (as hereinafter defined) is a valuable, special and unique asset of Company and agree that you will not disclose, transfer, use (or seek to induce others to disclose, transfer or use) any Confidential Information for any purpose other than disclosure to your authorized employees and agents who are bound to maintain the confidentiality of Confidential Information. You shall promptly notify Company in writing of any circumstances which may constitute unauthorized disclosure, transfer, or use of Confidential Information. You shall use best efforts to protect Confidential Information from unauthorized disclosure, transfer or use. You shall return all originals and any copies of any and all materials containing Confidential Information to Company upon termination of this Agreement for any reason whatsoever.
Confidential Information shall mean any and all of Company’s trade secrets, confidential and proprietary information and all other information and data of Company that is not generally known to the public or other third parties who could derive value, economic or otherwise, from its use or disclosure. Confidential Information shall be deemed to include technical data, know-how, research, product plans, products, services, customers, markets, software, developments, inventions, processes, formulas, technology, designs, drawings, engineering, hardware configuration information, marketing, finances or other business information disclosed directly or indirectly in writing, orally or by drawings or observation.

Intellectual Property Rights
You acknowledge and agree that all title, right and interest (including without limitation all copyright, trademarks and all other intellectual property rights) in all material or content supplied as part of the Website or App shall remain at all times vested in us or our licensors. You are permitted to use this material only as expressly authorised by us or our licensors.
You acknowledge and agree that the material and content contained in the Website or the App is made available for your personal, non-commercial use only and that you may download such material and content onto only one computer hard drive for such purpose. Any other use of the material and content of the Website or the App is strictly prohibited. You agree not to (and agree not to assist or facilitate any third party to) copy, save, modify, reproduce, transmit, publish, display, distribute or use for any purposes, whether commercial or non-commercial, the Website, the App or any software and information contained within the Website or the App without our permission, except to the extent necessarily required in order for you to display, use and navigate the Website or the App. You agree not to decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, rent, lease, loan, sublicense, commercially exploit or create derivative works from the Website or the App.
By submitting information, text, photos, or other content to us via the Website or the App, you grant us a right to use such materials at our own discretion including, without limitation, to edit, copy, reproduce, disclose, post and remove such materials from the Website or the App.
The texts, designs, images, audio, databases, logos, structure, trademarks and other elements of the Website and App are protected by intellectual property rights and industrial rights of us and / or third party owners who have duly authorized their inclusion in the Website or App.
All intellectual property rights related to the Services and / or the Website and / or the App remain the property of us or our group companies or third parties who have licensed the use of such rights.
You may not reproduce, copy, modify, adapt, publish, transmit, distribute or otherwise commercially exploit any material which is the subject of intellectual property rights related to the Services and / or the Website and / or the App.

Links to and from other websites
You may establish links to the Website or App from locations outside the Website or App provided: (a) where linking to the Website, you link only to the home page of the Website; (b) you do not remove or obscure, advertisements, the copyright notice or other notices on the Website or App; (c) you give us notice of such link by sending an e-mail message to us at cs@jobpedia.hk; (d) you do not link from a site or service that could be construed as distasteful or offensive or a site which infringes any third party intellectual property rights; and (e) you immediately stop providing links to the Website or App if notified by us to do so.
We may provide links to other websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the availability of such external websites or resources, and do not endorse and are not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including without limitation any advertising, products or other materials or services on or available from such websites or resources, nor for any damage, loss or offence caused or alleged to be caused by, or in connection with, the use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on such external websites or resources.
You may not create a database in electronic or structured manual form by systematically and/or regularly downloading, caching, printing and storing any or all of the content on the Website or App (by spidering or otherwise) and you may not frame, harvest or scrape any of the content on the Website or App or otherwise access such content for similar purposes.

Warranties and Limitation on Liability
Nothing in these Terms of Use shall exclude or limit our liability for fraudulent misrepresentation or for death or personal injury resulting from our negligence or that of our employees or our agents.
We do not accept any liability for damage to your computer system or loss of data that results from your use of the Website or App and we cannot guarantee that any files that you download are free from viruses, contamination or destructive features.
Whilst we will use reasonable endeavours to correct any errors or omissions as soon as practicable once they have been brought to our attention, we do not warrant that the information on the Website or App will be free from errors or omissions.
Whilst we will use reasonable endeavours to ensure a reasonable standard of integrity and reliability of the Website and App, we do not warrant that the Website or App will be available uninterrupted and in a fully operating condition.
Access to the Website or App may be suspended temporarily and without notice in the case of system failure, maintenance or repair or for reasons reasonably beyond our control.
The Website and App are provided on an “as is” and “as available” basis without any representation or endorsement and we make no warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, in relation to the Website or App, including but not limited to, implied warranties of satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement, compatibility, security, accuracy, conditions of completeness, or any implied warranty arising from course of dealing or usage or trade.
We will co-operate with any competent law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose information about you or your use of the Website or App. There may be other circumstances in which we may, in our reasonable discretion, disclose information about you or your use of the Website or App following a request to do so by legal counsel in good faith in relation to a dispute with you or a third party.

Indemnity
You agree to be fully responsible for (and fully indemnify us against) all claims, liability, damages, losses, costs and expenses, including legal fees, suffered by us and arising out of any breach of these Terms of Use by you or any other liabilities arising out of your use of the Website or the App, or the use by any other person accessing the Website or the App using your account.

Governing Law
Except as expressly provided otherwise, this Agreement is exclusively governed by, and will be construed under, the laws of the Hong Kong SAR, without regard to choice of law principles. Any arbitration necessary will be conducted in Hong Kong and be subject to Hong Kong laws too.

Special Promotions
Company may from time to time provide certain promotional opportunities, sweepstakes and contests to Users. All such promotions will be run at the sole discretion of Company, and can be activated, modified or removed at any time by Company without advance notification and the liability of any of Company’s Clients pursuant to such promotional opportunities, sweepstakes and contests shall be limited pursuant to these Terms of Service.

General Provisions
Failure by Company to enforce any provision(s) of this Agreement will not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and Company with respect to its subject matter. If any provision of this Agreement is found to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions will be enforced to the fullest extent possible, and the remaining provisions will remain in full force and effect. This Agreement will inure to the benefit of Company, its successors and assigns.

Contact
If you have any questions about these Terms of Use or any other terms that apply to the Services that we offer you can write to us at cs@jobpedia.hk

In the event of any conflict between the English and other language versions, the English version shall prevail.


使用條款
條款及細則
這些條款和細則（“使用條款”）規定了您可以訪問和使用我們的網站，下載和使用“Jobpedia”手機應用程式（“應用程式”）和訪問我們的服務，無論是通過網站，應用程式，或由我們或我們的集團公司通過其他方式提供（“服務”）。
網站和應用程式由OneJob Group Limited（“Jobpedia”/“公司”/“我們”/“我們的”）（根據香港法律註冊成立的有限責任公司）或我們的集團公司擁有和經營，並根據這些使用條款提供給您使用。 服務可能由我們或我們的集團公司提供或提供。 使用通過網站或應用程式提供的某些服務的使用條款可能會受到可能替代，完成和/或修改， 並受到這些使用條款的特定條款和細則的約束。 因此，在使用此類服務之前，您還必須仔細閱讀並接受這些服務的相應條款和細則。
通過使用網站和/或應用程式和/或任何服務，您被視為接受這些使用條款和任何附加條款和細則，如果您不同意這一點，您不能使用本網站，應用程式或接收相關服務。 使用網站或應用程式意味著接受您訪問它時適用的條款和細則。 因此，我們建議您定期查看這些使用條款以了解任何更改或更新。 公司保留隨時更改本協議的條款和細則或其與服務或應用程式相關的政策的權利，在服務或應用程式上發布本協議的更新版本後生效。 任何此類更改後繼續使用服務或應用程式即表示您同意此類更改

電子通信
接受這些使用條款或使用我們的任何服務的特定條款和細則，意味著您明確授權我們將您以下段落中指出的電子通信發送到您的家，手機和電子郵件地址。 此類授權包括發送與我們和與此平台相關的其他門戶以及第三方及其門戶（包括我們的集團公司）的產品和服務相關的商業和廣告通信。 我們目前通過電子郵件，短信或移動通知發送以下通訊：
建議和工作通知;
尋找就業的技巧、 報告、 趨勢等通訊;
商業通訊 （廣告、 市場研究和商業前景）。
通過填寫和發送電子註冊表，您同意我們發送與培訓和就業領域相關的電子通信。
本服務是容許多位用戶之間交流以完成工作任務的平台，惟本公司不對用戶之表現負責，亦不能控制其品質、時間、合法性以及服務供應之成敗或涉及到用戶客戶的其他方面，本公司亦不會就服務的完整性、責任或用戶的任何行為或疏漏承擔責任。本公司無法控制用戶所提供服務的品質、時間或合法性。

用戶資料審查
客戶及用戶在登記之前以及在使用服務的過程中（包括但不限於身份確認以及完整的背景調查），可能會被進行全方位的資料審查（如有需要使用第三方服務）。在此，用戶應當授權本公司在有需要時進行背景調查，所進行的背景調查的頻密程度應當符合當前法規在管轄司法權方面的規定。
儘管本公司可以對用戶進行上述背景調查，但本公司不能保證每位用戶都符合其聲明內容。因此，本公司不能也無法保證提供服務的準確性、身份的可靠性、背景調查資訊或其他任何本服務中所提供的資訊。
在與其他用戶進行互動的過程中，閣下應當隨時保持警惕，保護閣下的個人財產及安全。在此，閣下聲明本公司及其相關公司或授權公司免於有關責任。本公司及其相關公司或授權公司不對用戶在使用服務過程中所產生的任何索賠、受傷或損失負責任

註冊後我們的權利
通過向我們提供您的註冊個人信息，您同意我們和我們的集團公司可以在正常工作時間通過電話或電子郵件或其他與您的帳戶相關的方式與您聯繫。
通過向應用程式提交任何內容，您授予我們和我們的集團公司權利和永久許可免費使用，複製，修改，發布，翻譯，傳輸，通信，顯示或從這些內容創建任何衍生作品。 如果此類內容包括您的簡歷，則僅與您對服務的使用以及根據明確適用於此類服務的任何附加條款和細則有關。 我們保留權利在任何時間在不預先通知的情況下, 停用或刪除在應用程式任何內容。 如果我們在應用程式上停用或刪除您的任何內容，我們將使用合理的努力，但沒有義務提前與您聯繫。
我們保留刪除我們認為不准確，誤導，欺騙，可能誤導或欺騙的內容（包括但不限於任何簡歷或與職位空缺相關的信息）或不可接受的標準的權利。
如果您違反本使用條款下的任何義務，或者適用於向您提供的任何服務的其他條款和細則，我們可能會立即暫停或取消您的註冊，或我們自行作出合理決定。
如果我們無法驗證您提交給應用程式的任何同意，在您違反使用條款，無論是否能夠訪問應用程式和/或我們的服務，這些工作人員接觸條款或任何其他適用於您使用我們或任何集團公司提供的任何服務的條款和細則時向您提供的服務，我們保留自行決定採取我們的所有法律補救措施的權利包括但不限於從您的註冊刪除您的內容（包括但不限於任何簡歷）

可接受的服務使用
本服務可能含有人物介紹、電子郵件系統、網誌、資訊板、應用程式、職位發佈、網上聊天區、新聞組、論壇、社群團體以及／或用於與其他用戶進行交流的資訊或交流設備。閣下可能只使用團體領域來發送或接收適用於某一論壇的資訊及相關物件。網站的所有使用者（不論其有否註冊為會員）在使用網站時均嚴禁進行下列行為：
在網站上載任何含有不完整的、虛假的、不準確的、具誤導性、具欺詐性、涉及詆毀、涉及誹謗、涉及淫褻、涉及歧視、涉及騷擾、涉及威脅、涉及辱駡、涉及仇恨、涉及種族主義、非法的、不當的、具攻擊性的成分，或者具其他性質且與招聘／求職目的無關的資訊（包括但不限於招攬捐贈或業務、發佈無關的廣告、貿然發送電子郵件或進行直接或間接市場營銷）；
侵犯公司、其他使用者或任何第三方的知識產權權利或專有權利，或侵犯他人的私隱權、肖像權或其他個人權利；
在未獲得資料擁有人、賬戶擁有人或系統擁有人的允許的情況下使用相關資料或網站功能；
因病毒、損毀的文檔或其他材料而導致網站的運作中斷、受損害或受限制，或破壞網站的安全性，或者導致提供予任何使用者的服務受擾亂或受干擾；
違反條款及細則、違反私隱政策，或者違反香港或其他相關司法管轄區的任何適用法律及法規

合約終止和暫停
本公司和閣下之間的合約期限為無限期。本公司可能會在任何時候、以任何原因終止或暫停閣下使用本服務的權利。合約的終止將會以書面或電子郵件的形式提交給閣下。合約的終止在該通知交付後立即生效。
在任何情況下，如果閣下違反本協議（包括市場準則）的任何條款或在服務使用過程中本公司不時發佈的任何政策，或者本公司以其他方式發現閣下有從事不適當和／或攻擊性的行為，本公司可以終止或暫停閣下使用本服務。如果本公司因為以上這些原因終止或暫停閣下使用本服務，我們將不會退換閣下帳戶未使用的餘額。如果因任何理由本公司終止或暫停閣下的帳戶，閣下將被禁止用閣下自己的身份、假冒的或借來的用戶名，或任何第三方的名稱建立或註冊新帳戶，即使閣下可能代表第三方。除了終止或暫停閣下的帳戶，本公司還將保留採取適當法律行動的權利，包括但不限於尋求民事、刑事和強制賠償的權利。
即使閣下使用被終止或暫停服務的權利，本協定將對閣下繼續強制有效。
閣下可以透過停止使用所有服務來在任何時間終止本協議。所有根據其性質應在本協議期滿或終止應繼續有效的部分，在本協定期滿或終止生效以後繼續有效。

安全
閣下必須在本公司註冊並建立帳戶來使用本服務。閣下是閣下帳戶的唯一合法用戶。閣下有責任保證任何閣下或公司所提供的、用來獲得本服務的密碼及帳戶號碼的保密性。對於閣下的密碼和帳戶，閣下是唯一一個負有全責的人。本公司不會檢查任何用戶帳戶的使用情況，並特此否認從中衍生出的任何賠償責任。如果閣下懷疑任何未經授權的一方可能會使用閣下的密碼或帳戶或懷疑任何安全漏洞的情況，閣下應當立即聯繫公司。
提供閣下的手機號碼並使用本服務，代表閣下在此同意我們使用閣下的手機號碼進行通話和發送，以便提供和改進服務。本公司將不會評估任何電話或資訊的費用，但閣下的無線運營商可能會收取標準的訊息費或其他費用。
我們有權利（但不是義務）監控與本網站和應用程式相關的任何活動和內容。 我們可能調查任何報告的違反這些使用條款或投訴的行為，並採取我們認為適當的任何行動（可能包括但不限於發出警告，暫停，終止或附加條件和/或刪除任何材料從網站或應用程式）。

個人資料
「個人資料」是指閣下為使用本服務而提供給本公司或註冊過程相關的其他用戶的任何資訊和材料，包括但不限於在公共區域	使用而發佈或傳遞的資訊。閣下全權負責閣下的資訊，我們只是閣下網上發佈和傳播個人資訊的被動渠道。在本節中描述的用戶提供的材料被統稱為「用戶生成內容」。閣下在此聲明並向公司保證，閣下的資料（一）其非虛假、不準確、不完整或具誤	導性；（二）不是詐騙或涉及銷售假冒或被盜的物品的；（三）沒有侵犯任何第三方的版權、專利、商標、商業秘密或其他專	有權利、公開權或隱私權；（四）將不會違反任何法律、法令、條例或規章（包括但不限於有關出口管制、消費者保護、不公	平競爭、反歧視或虛假廣告）；（五）不含誹謗、中傷、非法恐嚇或非法騷擾的內容；（六）將含有淫穢、兒童色情或對未成	年人有害的內容；（七）不包含任何病毒、木馬程式、蠕蟲、定時炸彈，刪除或其他電腦編程程式和／或惡意軟體及其他電腦	病毒，旨在破壞、侵入、秘密截取或侵佔任何系統、資料或個人資訊；及（八）不會因互聯網服務供應商或其他客戶或供應商的服務對公司產生賠償責任或造成公司損失（全部或部分）。
本服務擁有與特定用戶檢討相關的用戶生成內容。該檢討的意見並不代表公司的意見，並未經公司審核透過。每位元客戶都應該自行研究某用戶的選擇是否正確。閣下同意，本公司不對任何用戶生成內容負責。
在此，閣下授予本公司一項非獨家、環球性的、永久、不可撤銷、免版稅的、無再授權（多層授權）的權利。本公司有權在任何已知和尚未知的媒體中行使所有版權、宣傳權以及任何「您的資料」含有的任何其他權利，來提供或改善服務。
每個提供給本公司的任何錄影帶、電影、唱片、照片、聲音或所有相關的工具、音樂或其他聲音效果，以換取使用本服務權利的用戶，在此不可撤銷地授予本公司的非獨家、繳足、免版稅、可轉讓、轉授、全球範圍內無限制、永久的權利：
使用用戶提供給本公司任何錄影帶、電影、紀錄或照片，使用、複製、修改用戶的圖片或創意衍生品、圖片輪廓和圖片具有物理相似性的其他複製品（如同樣可能出現在任何靜態相機照片和／或電影膠片或影片）（統稱為「物理相似性」），在所有的媒體的展覽（或與展覽相關的場景）、出品、展示、表演、傳播、廣播上，包括但不限於網際網路以及用戶任何與服務相關的影片或圖片。
在所有的媒體上，複製該用戶與服務相關的聲音以及其他所有相關的工具、音樂及其他音效（統稱「聲音」）。
在任何媒體的廣告、市場行銷以及／或服務推廣中使用，並允許他人使用該用戶的具有物理相似性的產品及聲音。
使用並允許他人使用該用戶與服務有關的名稱以及身份
每個用戶在此放棄所有權利，並使本公司免責，並不得對於相關方的已知或未知的行為提起訴訟，也不會因誹謗、侵犯隱私權、公開權、人格或任何類似的事情，或基於或關於本服務的使用及用戶的身份，肖像或聲音的使用對任何此類第三方提出任何索賠或訴訟。
所有用戶承認，本公司概不拖欠任何由使用用戶根據本協定所提供的錄音而產生的費用或其他報酬。無論是初次或後續傳輸或播放。用戶進一步確認，本公司概不負責因用戶的錄製或參與任何錄製包括錄音資料丟失而產生的任何費用。
收集個人資料聲明
關於工作申請的個人資料數據收集是自願的。 但是用戶驗證將僅在完成個人資料提交後進行。 個人資料數據包括但不限於照片，官方身份證明文件，地址證明，銀行帳號（用於工資發放）。 個人資料數據合用於確保用戶的合法性和在當地管轄區工作的權利以及工資服務
公司可以按業務用途所需，向閣下收集個人資料，當中包括 (但不局限於) 以下用途: 1. 與閣下建立及維持就業關係，2. 評估你是否適合擔任所申請的職位，用作與你商討初步的薪酬、花紅及福利，3. 通知閣下相關工作機會，提供培訓和就業資訊，為閣下安排工作，4. 市場推廣之用 (只限用於本公司之業務範圍) ，5.  維持合約及法定義務，6. 擬定統計數據， 7. 提供補償及福利，工資，評估，晉升和事業發展用途，8. 處理和應對法律索償及行動,遵從法庭命令及其他法律義務和法規要求。本人同意公司就招聘和就業有關的用途和任何必要的查詢核實上述資料，並向委託公司招聘員工的客戶(即閣下的準僱主)提供有關資料。

版權
您承認機密資訊（定義見下文）是公司寶貴、特殊和獨特的資產，並同意您將不會為任何目的而披露、轉讓、使用（或試圖誘使他人披露、轉讓或使用）除了告知給公開授權的員工。該員工也必須遵守隱私資訊中的相關規定。您應以書面形式將未經授權而披露、轉移或使用機密資訊的任何情況及時通知公司。您必須盡最大努力防止未經授權的披露、轉移或使用機密資訊。在合約因為任何原因結束的情況下，您應當返還全部含有公司機密資訊的原件和副本。所謂「機密資訊」是指公司的任何商業秘密、機密和專有資訊以及其他所有公司一般不為公眾及第三方所知的資訊資料。第三方可能透過披露或使用這些資料而獲得經濟利益。機密資訊應被視為包括直接或間接地以書面、口頭或透過圖紙或觀察進行披露的技術資料、技術知識、研發、產品規劃、產品、服務、客戶、市場、軟體、開發、發明、工藝、配方、工藝、設計、圖紙、工程設計、硬體配置資訊、市場行銷、財務或其他商業資訊。

知識產權
您承認並同意所有標題、 權利和利益 （包括但不限於所有版權、 商標和所有其他知識產權） 的所有材料或內容作為網站或應用程式提供的一部分，任何時候都歸屬於我們或我們的授權人的。只有得到我們或我們的授權人明確授權，你才允許使用這種材料。
您承認並同意，網站或應用程式中包含的內容和材料僅供您個人、 非商業使用，您只可以下載這種內容和材料到只有一台電腦的硬碟上使用。任何使用網站或應用程式的材料和內容在其他用途上是嚴格禁止。除了一定程度展示使用和瀏覽網站或應用程式的內容和材料，未經我們允許, 您同意不會 （並同意不協助或便利向第三方）去複製、 保存、 修改、 重現、 傳輸、 發佈、 展示、 分發或使用網站/應用程式或任何軟體和上所包含的資訊作任何用途，無論是否商業或非商業的。您同意不會編譯、 彙編、 出租、 租賃、 貸款、 發放許可、 商業利用或從網站或應用程式創建衍生作品
通過提交資訊、 文本、 照片或其他內容到我們通過網站或應用程式，您給予我們的權利使用這種材料包括但不限於，編輯，複製、 再現、 披露、 發佈和刪除此類材料的網站或應用程式
文本、 設計、 圖像、 音訊、 資料庫、 徽標、 結構、 商標和其他元素的網站和應用程式的知識產權和工業產權的保護, 我們和/或第三方擁有人獲有正式授權的網站或應用程式中將其列入
與服務相關的所有知識產權或本網站和/或應用程式仍然是我們或我們的公司集團或具有許可使用這種權利的第三方具有許可使用
你不會去重現、 複製、 修改、 適應、 發佈、 傳送、 分發或其他商業目的而利用, 因這有知識產權是有關的服務和/或本網站和/或應用程式任何的主體材料
和其他網站的連結
您可以從網站或應用程式之外的位置建立指向本網站或應用程式的鏈接：（a）在連接到本網站時，您僅連接到本網站的主頁; （b）您不會刪除或隱藏網站或應用程式上的版權聲明或其他通知; （c）你可以通過發送電子郵件給我們cs@jobpedia.hk通知我們這樣的鏈接; （d）您不能從可被解釋為令人討厭或令人反感的網站或服務或違反任何第三方知識產權的網站鏈接; 和（e）如果我們通知您，您立即停止提供網站或應用程式的鏈接。
我們可能提供其他網站或資源的鏈接。 您承認並同意我們不負責這種外部網站或資源的可用性，並且不認可和不負責這直接或間接針對這些網站的隱私慣例或內容，通過或關於使用或依賴此類外部網站或資源上提供的任何此類內容，商品或服務，包括但不限於此類網站或資源上的或從這些網站或資源獲得的任何廣告，產品或其他材料或服務，也不包括由於或指稱造成的任何損害，損失或犯罪
您不得通過系統和/或定期下載，緩存，打印和存儲網站或應用程式中的任何或所有內容（通過spidering或其他方式），以電子或結構化手動形式創建數據庫， 刪除網站或應用程式上的任何內容或以其他方式訪問此類內容以用於類似目的。.

保證和賠償責任限制
這些使用條款中的任何內容均排除或限制我們對由於我們的疏忽或我們的員工或我們的代理造成的欺詐性失實陳述或死亡或人身傷害的責任。
我們不對您的計算機系統損壞或由於您使用本網站或應用程式而導致的數據丟失不承擔任何責任，我們不能保證您下載的任何文件沒有病毒，污染或破壞性功能。
雖然我們在提請我們注意後，將盡快在可行的情況下盡力糾正任何錯誤或遺漏，但我們不保證網站或應用程式中的信息不會有錯誤或遺漏。
雖然我們將盡合理努力確保網站和應用程式的完整性和可靠性的合理標準，但我們不保證網站或應用程式將不間斷且在完全運行狀態下可用。
訪問網站或應用程式可能會暫停，如果系統故障，維護或修理或由於合理地超出我們控制的原因，恕不另行通知。
網站和應用程式以“原樣”和“可用”基礎提供，沒有任何代表或認可，我們不對與網站或應用程式有關的任何形式的擔保，包括但不限於對於滿足質量，適用於特定目的，非侵權，兼容性，安全性，準確性，完整性條件或由交易或使用或交易過程中產生的任何默示保證的暗示保證。
我們將與任何主管執法機關或法院命令合作，要求或指示我們披露有關您或您使用本網站或應用程式的信息。 在其他情況下，我們可以根據我們的合理判斷，披露有關您或您使用本網站或應用程式的信息，如果法律顧問真誠地就您與您或第三方的爭議提出請求 。

賠償
你同意全面負責 （並充分賠償我們） 的所有索賠、 責任、 損害、 損失、 費用和開支，包括法律費用，受到我們和任何違反這些條款的使用, 由您使用網站或應用程式或訪問網站或使用您的帳戶的任何其他人使用而產生的損失。

適用法律
除非另有明文規定，本協議須受香港特別行政區的法律管限及解釋，而不考慮法律適用原則。任何必要的仲裁將於香港進行，並受香港法律管制。


特別促銷
公司可隨時給用戶提供一定的促銷機會、抽獎和比賽。所有這些優惠將由公司自行決定，並可以在任何時候由公司啟動、修改或刪除，無需預先通知。公司的客戶、抽獎和比賽應當遵守這些條款服務。

總則
本公司違反本協議的任何規定不得解釋為放棄任何條款或權利。本協定是您與本公司之間的完整協議。如果本協議的任何條款被認定為無效或不可執行，其餘條款將被強制執行，其餘條款將在最大程度上仍然具有十足效力及作用。本協議的生效代表公司、其繼承人和受讓人的利益。

連絡人
如果您有任何問題關於這些使用條款或任何其他條款，適用於服務，我們提供你可以寫信給我們 cs@jobpedia.hk

本使用條款應以英文版為準, 中文版只做參考之用.
"</string>
</resources>